Mvxy.site
Sorry I'm late.
I would copy something
and the machine messed up.
- We have been waiting for a while.
- I'm sorry.
My name is Anita and I am new here,
just like you.
I am a physical education teacher and also have to
substitute as class director.
Then you know it.
Everyone can introduce themselves by first name
and tell something fun about yourself.
In that way
let's get to know each other a little.
We start with you.
My name is Nora and
a fun thing about me is that I...
I spend 20,000 on makeup every year.
My name is Amalie and...
I'm damn good at it
to play triangle.
Louise. Have not applied to this school.
Mariam, I like ice cream.
Pernille, I have done
my own piercings.
Mina, I have been going to yoga for four years.
My name is Truls
and cry when I chop onions.
My name is Robin and...
I'm looking forward
to get to know you better.
My name is Markus
and I have a big cock.
Okay.
Then I suggest we just…
Sorry, my memory is bad.
- What was your name?
- Anita.
Do you have something fun to tell?
Okay.
My name is Anita-
- and I've been at it
with gymnastics.
Now they have arranged a screening
so you can see the school.
You can come now,
because I think they are waiting.
Today is Hasse's birthday
Hooray, hooray, hooray
He will surely get a present
as he wished
With yummy chocolate and cookies too
Congratulations!
- Come in.
- Thanks, Dad.
Hello!
- Mom is selling the house.
- I didn't know that.
She is going to buy an apartment closer to the city center.
- It gets lonely in such a big house.
- Of course.
It will be strange not to come
back to that house.
I have been there all my childhood.
- All the memories.
- It's getting weird.
- It will be good for Mai-Britt.
- Yes.
How are things going for you?
With me? Yes, I think...
How nice it is with false eyelashes.
It's great.
- It's going well.
- You have become a teacher?
- How nice.
- She has been a teacher for a week.
We'll see how long it lasts.
Yes, we'll see.
- Weren't you going to travel?
- Well, to Budapest.
Anita started working,
so I moved it to October.
We have a wedding anniversary,
so it fits well.
- I understand.
- Romantic.
How long are you in Frankfurt?
See you on Friday.
Sleep well.
It is grouse hunting, fishing,
food, drink and lies.
- It's fantastic.
- That sounds awesome.
That's the best I know.
It's ten days in the life with the guys
when I just relax.
- Is it a tradition?
- It's actually the twenty-fifth year.
Come on!
- Anita?
- Can we go to the bathroom?
- It's probably going well.
Hurry back.
Good job, Markus.
You look good too.
Hello.
- Damn!
- Sorry.
I didn't know about me
would clear my throat.
- Here you stand...
- Or just stand still.
...in the dark.
How has the start been?
Very good, I think.
- And you're having a good time?
- I enjoy myself here.
No rotten eggs?
- You think about the students?
- Yes.
No, they are so cozy.
How nice to hear.
They are different, of course.
- Everyone is nice, but...
- That's nice.
- That people are different?
- That's good.
I will have...
I'm done here.
Trine-Lise?
Sorry, I just…
You said I would take over
as class principal-
- for her who is on sick leave.
I just wonder how long I
must have that responsibility.
- It's about a couple of months.
- Yes.
I feel that I actually
lacks the right skills.
If you are thinking about something
you just ask me
Okay, thanks.
Stop!
Now that's enough!
What are you doing?!
- He's so fucking ugly!
- Fucking pussy!
You are so ugly!
Anita! Come here?
- Are you taking him to the teacher's room?
- Marcus?
At once.
Come with me, Markus.
Come with me. Come again.
Of.
- He poured iced tea down my neck.
- Why that?
I know damn it, I don't know him.
What a fucking moron.
You should go to the school sister
and see if you need stitches.
It's probably not needed.
Are you dizzy?
- Sure?
- It's going well.
- No pressure behind the eyes?
- Nothing.
- May I feel your neck?
- Yes.
Then we'll see.
Does this hurt?
- No.
- Not?
- This, then?
- You feel it, but it doesn't hurt.
The neck feels good.
Take it easy today, it's probably best.
I heard you broke your neck.
Have you heard that?
- Is that true?
- Yes, that's true.
It's been a long time.
What happened?
I would qualify for a competition
and missed a somersault.
Exactly that.
Are you recovered now?
Yes. Although I have
a couple of screws in the back.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
- Can I feel?
- On the screws?
I don't know if it's possible
know them. Maybe the one.
It is in the middle.
I feel it.
There it is.
You don't seem so limb.!
No, in that way I was lucky.
You'll have time for the math.
Walk carefully.
- Hello, Astrid.
- Hello.
Markus?
Anita // 20:43 - Forget what happened
today, it should never have happened.
Cool day today?
Excuse?
I just said
that it was an awesome day.
That was it.
You can count on that sort of thing
when working at a school.
I don't really know that.
It's fun with a little action.
That something happens.
That it's not just clean
and cleaned all the time.
Or?
But you talk to the parents?
Is it my responsibility?
It's so badly forced.
- Sure.
- That's good.
What's going on? Is it something fun?
Tell.
- No, it just...
Tell me now.
- What is it?
- Just a friend who was joking.
What was she joking about?
Tell me what she was joking about.
It seemed so fun.
It's a long story
and difficult to explain.
Now I'm taking a weekend.
- You're staying?
- A little while.
Shall we have a beer?
Or maybe a glass of wine.
No, thanks.
That's great.
Of course it is.
But...
You must have such a good time.
Turn off when you leave.
Otherwise, people get mad.
Oh no.
Or maybe, you never know.
Have a good time.
No.
Has it been a good week?
And.
I think it has been nice.
How has your week been?
It's been busy,
but that's the way it should be.
The white roses in the aisle,
who are they from
They were outside the door
when i got home.
Was there no card?
No.
There wasn't.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
Dude!
- My God, Anita?
- It's me.
- Hello, Unni.
- It was a long time ago.
- It wasn't yesterday.
- Really not.
- Hi:.
- Hello.
You are the same.
We practiced gymnastics together
many years ago.
- Anita Lønstrup.
- Lars Simonsen.
Nice.
Beat is down.
We know each other, Markus
and do not need health.
A little thing before we start.
Markus has football training
seven o'clock.
It's fine if we are
finish a little earlier.
- It's probably going well.
- You can come a little late, right?
He has a match this weekend.
How important can this be?
- The guy threw soda at him.
- Lars.
- Can I say something?
- Absolutely.
I am very sorry
for what happened.
It was the wrong way to react.
I am totally against violence.
I think violence is wrong.
He has learned a lesson.
Then maybe we're done here?
This school has a strict policy
regarding events like this.
I promised to say hello
from Simen's parents-
-and say they considered
a police report.
- But they changed their mind.
- Now you can give up.
I promised to say it.
Don't tell me to calm down.
What do you mean, really?
The thing is that the principal-
- has decided that Markus can't
come along on the class trip to Berlin.
You have got to be kidding.
But he has started collecting money.
His grandmother, who has a low pension
-have bought ten packages
with the world's driest biscuits.
- Ugh?
- We must not lose our temper.
But isn't that a bit strict?
This is not my decision.
- The school trip is the highlight of the year.
- I understand how it feels.
You know how they are at that age.
Is it really that serious?
The school has this strict policy.
- It's zero tolerance.
- It's absolutely incredible.
It's just the way it is.
You must not fight.
If someone throws something at you
you fight back.
It is not something you can influence.
We can talk about this
and get back to you.
Maybe we should talk to a lawyer...
Then I just wonder
if you had more questions?
No, not right now.
Then we finish here
and keep in touch.
- Have a good time.
Be well, Unni.
- We can talk more.
- I'll call you.
Are you coming home for dinner?
No!
Hello.
This is not wise, Markus.
This is bloody stupid!
Shall I drive you home?
- I ride a bike.
- Well, you ride a bike.
Okay, it's...
It is very good for the environment.
No, but... Yep.
Then you just get...
It got weird.
I noticed it right away.
Very strange.
- Very strange.
- Good that you noticed.
A hug then.
You smell great.
- See you tomorrow.
What are you doing this weekend?
I don't know. Gardening.
Gardening? Cool.
Have a great time.
Come on! The West!
You must catch up on English.
Pick up the pace!
Those who do not cycle may jog.
Anita // 16.52
Thanks for last time. Hanging out tonight?
Markus
Sorry
Marcus
Going to play a match in Drammen :(
Anita - How about next week?
We can cook pizza.
Read
Hey, you came anyway.
Are you feeling better?
- Much better.
- Come in.
How nice.
we just ate
so if you are hungry…
No, thanks.
But you might want some wine?
No, thanks. I don't drink.
Girls, now you have to say hello to Anita.
Anita and I are
old gym buddies.
Then she suddenly appeared
as Markus' teacher.
And Robin's teacher.
He has talked a lot about you.
- What good. Anita Lønstrup.
- Jenny.
My colleagues at the Norwegian Food Safety Authority,
Randi and Anne.
- Anita.
- Randi.
Finally we have Eli,
who lives further down the street.
- Nice.
- Sit down.
- Sit here.
- It's free here.
Are you ready for some dessert?
I have baked cheesecake.
Without palm oil this time.
Fantastic.
So you are the bookworms?
Yes, we are.
There were more of us, but people drop out,
for various reasons.
- What are you reading?
- "Without a Thread" by Jens Bjørneboe.
Is it good, or?
I think it was very good.
Entertainment in any case.
It was more reminiscent of youth.
There are so many black souls.
- People are completely...
- Yes.
I thought it would be
much more explicit.
It was banned.
It still is.
You should read "Sodom's 120 Days"
by Marquis de Sade.
- Is it new?
- No.
It is very old,
from the 18th century.
1700, then it is very old.
Then I don't know if I can take it.
- How did the match go?
- Good.
- Did you win?
- A draw.
- Come and say hello.
- Is it Markus?
There we have the soccer star.
How big he has become.
His father up in the day.
Did you score?
- I mostly sat on the bench.
- He's not in shape.
I can't hold myself.
I have to give you a hug.
You have grown so big!
They are soaring.
Where do the years go?
You two know each other.
It has happened
some PE lessons now.
Both ghost ball and other activities.
I just said that Robin brags about
how much fun you have in the lessons.
It is very nice.
Why are you here?
- Why am I here?
- Yes?
You'll have to ask your mother.
I invited her to the book club.
- I thought it might fit.
- It's very fun.
I have to shower.
You can have such a nice time.
He is so beautiful.
- Does he have a girlfriend?
- No, he doesn't seem that interested.
You know that, right?
- What?
- Because you are his teacher.
- Excuse me?
- If he has a girlfriend.
I don't know anything about that.
- But I don't think so.
- It's coming.
How about love for you?
You get straight to the point.
It's going well.
- You're not single?
- No, I'm married.
Were there any children?
Hasse, as he is called,
have two adult daughters.
- Are you all right?
- It works very well.
Someone has it.
Don't start now.
- Did you have more wine?
- Yes, I have more wine.
Unni, do you have a toilet?
Up the stairs and to the left.
- Hello?
- It's me.
Anita.
Sorry, didn't mean to.
- There is a toilet further down the hall.
- Thank you.
“Obviously I wanted to go out straight away
and look at the city"-
-"but a promise is a promise
and I stayed in my room."
“I bathed, washed myself
thoroughly everywhere…”
"...and went to bed with a book."
"It was 'Fiskerjenten' by Bjørnson.
"If the travel fund was increased
with 5000 Norwegian kroner"-
- "everything would change."
“Actually, I should thank you
Dr. Petterson for everything."
“I thought it would have been nice
to have him here in bed."
“Just lie in his arms
and have a good time."
“I think I was dreaming
about him that night."
It's so nice.
- Do you think it was nice?
- Delicious.
Where did you go?
Sorry, I was feeling
suddenly not good.
I just needed some air
and water on the face.
- But now I feel better.
- Eat some cheesecake.
It was delicious.
You must be good at baking.
I am very fond of that one.
- Was it good?
- I will be completely...
You seem healthier now.
- I became very energetic.
- What do you have in the cake?
Marcus:
Isn't that the song from Armageddon?
Anita:
What is it?
Marcus:
A movie
Anita:
We have to see it
Mine. Mike. Trick.
- Robin.
- Amalie. Pernille.
- Yes.
- Mariam. Eline.
- Marcus.
- He is sick.
Okay. Olivia. Maya Emma. Nora.
Then we go in.
Anita H 09:31
How is the shape?
There is something not right.
Okay?
- Haven't you noticed?
- No.
What would it be?
A link.
Fin.
That was what was missing.
We have to leave.
I'm coming.
You are a little absent.
- Do you think?
- Yes, I do.
Okay, no.
Maybe I'm just a little tired.
- Who are you texting all the time?
- Just school stuff.
School stuff? What then?
A colleague who has
problem with a student.
A colleague? Who is that?
- Her name is Elisabeth.
- Elisabeth?
What is the problem?
It's boring to talk about.
She asks if I have any advice.
Does she ask you for advice? A new teacher.
I'm looking forward to Budapest.
It will be lovely.
It had been a long time since we were there.
Thank you.
How many will we be?
It's just us in the department.
So a bunch of lawyers and me?
No, most of them
have had enough with their partners.
Can you refrain from saying
that you started working?
- Why that?
- Hey there.
Hello, nice.
Why that?
This is Sofia, our new lawyer.
- Anita.
- Sofie, nice.
Henriette is a co-owner.
- Anita.
- Nice to meet you, Anita.
- Haven't you met?
- I don't think so.
You have been with us for a long time.
- Four years?
- Five years now.
It's a long time.
We work closely together.
You were in Frankfurt last time.
Very good lawyer,
I must say.
It was nice to meet.
I have heard very good things.
How was it in Davos, Henriette?
It was actually absolutely fantastic.
Anita
Did you get my message?
I was just supposed to work.
I actually thought we should
have our conference there.
It's altitude training
to just lie in the hotel.
It's very loud, the hotel.
- What did you say?
- It seems to be high.
It was at 2000.
It's actually loud.
- How was training?
Legs feel heavy,
but it is so beautiful.
Who did you train with?
With Marianne and them.
You haven't joined yet?
Where were we last year? Paris it was.
- It's a wonderful city.
- Yes, incredibly nice.
The Eiffel Tower and...
Paris was absolutely fantastic.
The trip was brilliant,
but it would be fun to do something new.
Marcus
I have never felt better
Or so I thought...
- The babysitter?
- No.
Paid more?
It's just work stuff.
How long have you been married?
- Hasse and me?
- No.
- Yes, Hasse and you.
- Five years until the fall.
Five years? It's not that long.
Not by and large.
Are you pregnant?
No, I'm not.
- I just...
- No, then.
- Would you like a glass of wine?
- No, thanks.
Did you meet on the Danmarksferjan?
No, we met online.
- Where?
- Online.
Online.
They met online.
That kind of online dating.
Was it an app, or?
You post a profile
and see if anyone matches.
- Isn't it just about lying down?
- No.
The one I want to sleep with,
I agree with that.
Isn't that so?
Hasse, I'm just going to the bathroom.
Surely that's good?
Is there such an app
for a father of five?
Hi, it's Markus.
I can't answer right now.
I just have to go for a ride.
- Hi:.
- Hello.
- How cool you are.
Tack.
Actually, I'm out with my husband.
I just wanted to talk to Markus.
- He wasn't at school today.
- Wasn't he?
Didn't you know that?
Another student said he was sick.
No, I don't think so.
At least he missed
compulsory education.
It's stupid in high school and
we have an exam in that subject next week.
And...
- I just wanted to inform him.
- Now he is in training.
- What training?
- On the football field.
The one at school? Okay.
We're going to the cinema
and see Almodovar's latest.
- "The Flesh of Love."
- Med Palma de Rossy.
I'll go there and tell you.
No problem.
- Excuse me? Have you seen Markus?
- No.
Long, dark, short hair.
Plays in the junior team.
- Isn't he with Robin?
- He probably went to the port.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Absolutely sure?
I just...fell in love.
It's not a big deal,
I take one step at a time.
Just like…
I just have to…
- Hi:.
- Hello.
- Thank you for last time.
What's going on?
I just wonder why you
not responding to my messages.
- I've been busy.
- Busy?
- I thought you were sick.
- I have slept badly.
- Are you worried about something?
- Not really.
...take it easy
and carefully in the future.
What is it?
Are we talking about the same person?
- I think so.
- Mine in class.
And.
Marcus? Hello!
can you come here
I just want to talk a little.
You didn't believe
that we talked about us?
No, are you insane?
It would have been shady.
It had looked that way.
You are 50 years old, as well.
Did you get together with Mina recently?
Together, I don't know. We are dating.
Cozy, she seems to be
a nice girl.
Yes, she... She's pretty.
Have you spoken to the principal?
about the trip to Berlin?
Can I come with you to Berlin?
Have you talked to the principal about it?
- No.
- Not?
Do it then.
- Do you want to taste?
- No, thanks.
- Do you need a ride somewhere?
- I'm going to the boys.
Are you opening or not?
The lock. It is locked.
Child lock.
A thousand thanks.
See you on Monday.
- Fett. Aerobics.
- Aerobics.
Excuse.
Seriously, she sucked him.
Have a nice weekend.
The trip to Budapest.
What do you say about it?
What do I say about it?
I think it will be very nice.
Budapest is absolutely wonderful.
A great city.
But it won't be as good
if we wait until spring?
Why that?
It's just a bit much now.
I have two days in Frankfurt,
I'm going to London-
-and you seem to have a lot too.
Jo...
It's totally fine,
we can take it later.
We can talk about it again in the spring.
It is much better. Warmer.
Just.
There is certainly a crisis at work.
Thanks for the good food.
You are a great cook.
See you tomorrow. Sleep well.
Sleep well.
Give me five laps around the school
at a leisurely pace!
Come on! Then we'll meet here afterwards.
Come on! No whining!
Mina?
are you there
It's Anita.
Of.
What has happened?
If you can't open, we'll talk a bit.
But ugh then.
What has happened?
Someone has posted a card on me
on Facebook.
So what cards?
- A shitty nude picture.
- Ugh then.
Who does something like that?
Don't know.
It was Markus who took the card.
- You think Markus posted it?
- I don't know, maybe.
It's absolutely terrible in that case.
Ugh, terrible.
But listen here.
Now I don't know you well
and I don't know Markus either.
But you seem to be
an incredibly beautiful girl-
-who should have a nice boyfriend and
I don't think Markus is kind.
Do you hear that? He is not kind.
- You shouldn't have it that way.
- No.
Or how? Come on.
This was not fun.
Poor you.
How about your mother?
It's not my mother.
But then Ragnhild.
I haven't spoken to her
for many years.
- How is Markus doing?
- Just fine.
I think so.
We haven't talked much,
he seems to be busy.
What do you mean by that?
He seems to have got a girlfriend.
That's right, she...
- Mine in the class?
- I know.
- Incredibly sweet girl.
- I probably don't agree with that.
- You know her.
- I won't say anything.
- I think it's good for him.
- Good that you believe that.
She is very good at
to appear cute.
Pulls the ponytail and...
A damn dangerous girl, I think.
When you say it
so they had a fight the other day.
But given the sounds I heard
last night they probably got over it.
My God, they are active
at that age.
- They're doing it. Were we like that?
- Not me.
Markus?
Markus!
- Where is it?
- I have to talk to you.
- You have to stop stalking me.
- Stalk you?
I'm looking for you for a reason.
I have something important to say.
Come on!
What the hell is that?
I am pregnant.
How far along are you?
No, it's... You know that.
That's about six weeks.
- Are you absolutely sure that...?
- Yes.
I think it's similar to you.
Are you not on the pill?
No, I don't.
My husband sterilized himself,
so it hasn't been…
How good.
Bra.
Don't be sad, Markus.
Markus...
Ugh then.
Don't be sad.
It's hard to see you like this.
It will be alright.
Okay? It will be good.
We can do it together.
I'm so stupid.
No, don't say that.
You are absolutely amazing.
You are not stupid.
Okay?
But then we agree?
That this stays between us?
Okay?
What are you thinking about?
- You don't say anything to Mina, do you?
- If I say something to Mina?
No, of course not.
Why would I tell her?
This is between us.
Markus, this is our secret.
Do you understand that?
It's just about you and me.
But then see you soon?
- Yes.
- Or how?
Send a message.
Don't forget
to answer my messages.
I get so stressed
when you don't answer.
Respond quickly,
so I don't get so stressed.
Nice.
See you.
- Hello then.
Hello. is that you
Are you out and about? Shopping a little?
I've only tried on one skirt.
Peach.
- Maybe it is.
I'm just out looking.
My mother turns 67 years old.
Congratulations. I'll just pay.
I have thought of one thing.
Have you heard any rumors about…
If a student from VG1,
who had it together with their teacher?
I haven't heard anything about that.
Not anything.
But I'll check that out.
Because I...
I passed by outside the school cafeteria.
Some girls were chatting
and it became very concrete.
I was just wondering
if you knew anything.
That's what girls say
very strange things.
- How did it feel?
- It was beautiful.
I'm parked wrong
and may come back later.
See you.
Anita // 18.28 Why don't you answer?
when I call? We need to talk!
TIME
Hello.
Why don't you answer when I call?
Have you called? I didn't know that.
i miss you
Your beautiful face.
Your soft skin, the warmth of your body.
Do you feel like it?
to come to me tonight?
My husband is away,
we can make pizza...
...watch a football match,
just the two of us. Damn it!
Everything is here.
What are you doing, Anita?
Are you pregnant?
No.
If you touch my son one more time...
Then I'll kill you.
- Do you understand?! I'll kill you!
- I understand.
Do you have a spare room?
A spare room, yes.
We can probably arrange that.
- How long are you staying?
- I don't know.
No.
I need a card
to register.
So there.
Yes, as you probably know, it has-
-flourished some rumors
the last few days.
When that happens-
-it tends to lead
to some misunderstanding.
It is best that Anita herself gets
explain what has happened.
Then you can pass it on
to the students.
I just feel…
No matter what you think or say
then you are right.
As for everything.
You guys are so damn relieved
that you are not me.
I don't understand
why should i stand here...
It is completely pointless.
Do you want me to say that...?
I think they need to
an explanation.
This should not have happened.
I just don't understand…
It's so fucking unnecessary.
Damn, this is totally…
Anita.
Hase?
Hass!
I...didn't know that people
would react so harshly.
People got so upset.
School and...mother.
It is completely...
It was the same thing
with the trip to Berlin.
It worked out, but…
Hasse is a good guy.
But you will surely find another
good guy with whom you can have children.
Of...
You are a good woman.
Good luck with everything.